<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carman Terblanche</title>
    <link>carmanillustrations.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Carman Terblanche</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="carmanillustrations.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>carmanillustrations.com/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 10:39:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>carmanillustrations.com/about-me/</guid>
      <description>I am a videographer who has a keen eye for images and scenery. I love experimenting with making good scenes look great!
Early Life I was born in Johannesburg, South Africa and grew up in Pretoria for most my life. I loved doing everything! From acting to sports to music and probably anything you can imagine. Finding a passion that sticks was difficult, so I tried combining them to make something new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>carmanillustrations.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 10:39:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>carmanillustrations.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>CARMAN TERBLANCHÉ Waterbok1 Kleinfontein, Pretoria, 1000 | +27 727 072 657 | carmanillustrations@gmail.com
EDUCATION Monash University Degree obtained 2017-2020 This is a Computer Science degree with a major in mobile systems. This includes drones, self-driving cars and mobile phones. We learn skills like application development for Android, understanding Networks and how a computer functions on a hardware, as well as a software level. This degree taught me teamwork, research and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rates</title>
      <link>carmanillustrations.com/rates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 10:39:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>carmanillustrations.com/rates/</guid>
      <description>   Filming / Production      Rate Type Price   Hourly R 250   1/2 Day R850   Full Day R 1500       Post-Production      Rate Type Price   Hourly R200    *Additional R2000 per day for equipment and travel flat rate Go Home </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>carmanillustrations.com/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 10:39:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>carmanillustrations.com/skills/</guid>
      <description>Skill levels: novice - intermediate - skilled - professional - expert
Photography I have over 5 years experience in photography, which was the main driving force towards video production and film. I have mainly photographed wildlife, but have experience in experimental, pet and fashion photography.
Skill Level: Skilled
 Videography/Camera Work I am quite proficient in operating cameras and visualising ideas that I have to bring the best images to life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
